{
    "subject": "Eleanor_Boardman",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "King_Vidor",
    "human_readable": "Eleanor Boardman is married to King Vidor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9746499061584473,
            "question": "When were Eleanor Boardman and King Vidor married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9346567392349243,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Eleanor Boardman and King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9040210843086243,
            "question": "Who is Eleanor Boardman married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7559839487075806,
            "question": "Do Eleanor Boardman and King Vidor have any children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7544679641723633,
            "question": "Where did Eleanor Boardman and King Vidor live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5945926308631897,
            "question": "Did Eleanor Boardman and King Vidor collaborate on any projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48739704489707947,
            "question": "Is Eleanor Boardman an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46568742394447327,
            "question": "What is King Vidor known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35201913118362427,
            "question": "Was King Vidor a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2871014475822449,
            "question": "What films did King Vidor direct?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eleanor Boardman is married to King Vidor.",
            "html": "yago_5829_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was King Vidor a director?",
            "html": "yago_5829_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is King Vidor known for?",
            "html": "yago_5829_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Eleanor Boardman an actress?",
            "html": "yago_5829_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5829_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Eleanor Boardman is married to King Vidor. This is stated explicitly in multiple documents, including files 1.txt, 45.txt, and others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that King Vidor and Eleanor Boardman were married from 1926 until their divorce in 1933, thus supporting the statement that Eleanor Boardman is married to King Vidor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}